A new study from researchers uncovers the kinds of infrastructure improvements that would make the biggest difference in increasing the number of electric cars on the road, a key step toward reducing greenhouse gas emissions from transportation.
研究人员开展的一项新研究揭示了哪些类型的基础设施改进最能增加上路行驶的电动汽车数量，而增加电动汽车数量是减少交通运输领域温室气体排放的关键一步。
The researchers found that installing charging stations on residential streets, rather than just in central locations such as shopping malls, could have an outsized benefit.
研究人员发现，在住宅区街道上安装充电站，而不仅仅是在购物中心等中心地段安装，可能会带来格外大的好处。
They also found that adding on high-speed charging stations along highways and making supplementary vehicles more easily available to people who need to travel beyond the single-charge range of their electric vehicles could greatly increase the vehicle electrification potential.
他们还发现，沿高速公路增设快速充电站，并让那些需要出行的距离超出自家电动汽车单次充电续航里程的人更容易用上补充车辆，可能会大大提升车辆电气化的潜力。
The findings are reported in Nature Energy, in a paper by associate professor of energy studies Jessika Trancik, graduate student Wei Wei, and others.
这些研究结果发表在《自然·能源》期刊的一篇论文中，论文作者为能源研究副教授杰西卡·特兰西克、研究生魏伟等人。
The researchers developed a new methodology to identify charging solutions that would conveniently fit into people’s daily activities.
研究人员开发了一种新方法，用来找出能方便地融入人们日常活动的充电方案。
They used data collected from GPS tracking devices in cars, as well as survey results about people’s daily driving habits and needs, including detailed data from local areas and more general data from the country as a whole.
他们使用了从车载GPS追踪设备收集的数据，以及关于人们日常驾驶习惯和需求的调查结果，其中既有来自地方的详细数据，也有全国整体层面较为概括的数据。
Greatly increasing the penetration of electric cars into the personal vehicle fleet is a central feature of climate mitigation policies at local and national levels, Trancik says.
特兰西克说，大幅提高电动汽车在私家车保有量中的渗透率，是地方和国家层面减缓气候变化政策的一大核心要素。
A goal of this study was “to better understand how to make these plans for rapid vehicle electrification a reality,” she adds.
她补充说，这项研究的目标之一是“更好地理解如何让这些快速实现车辆电气化的计划成为现实”。
In deciding how to prioritize different kinds of improvements in vehicle charging infrastructure, she says, “the approach that we took methodologically was to emphasize building a better understanding of people’s detailed energy-consuming behavior, throughout the day and year.”
她说，在决定如何为车辆充电基础设施的各类改进排定优先次序时，“我们在方法上采取的思路是，着重加深了解人们全天、全年的具体耗能行为。”
To do that, “we examine how different people are moving from location to location throughout the day, and where they are stopping,” she says.
她说，为此，“我们考察不同的人在一天中如何从一个地点移动到另一个地点，又在哪些地方停留。”
“And from there we’re able to look at when and where they would be able to charge without interrupting their daily travel activities.”
“然后据此，我们就能考察他们可以在什么时间、什么地点充电，而不打断日常出行活动。”
The team looked at both regular daily activities and the variations that occur over the course of a year.
该团队既考察了常规的日常活动，也考察了一年当中出现的种种变化。
“The longitudinal view is important for capturing the different kinds of trips that a driver makes over time, so that we can determine the kinds of charging infrastructure needed to support vehicle electrification,” Wei says.
魏伟说：“纵向视角对于捕捉驾驶者在一段时间内的各类出行十分重要，这样我们就能确定支持车辆电气化需要哪些类型的充电基础设施。”
While the vast majority of people’s daily driving needs can be met by the range provided by existing lower-cost electric cars, as Trancik and her colleagues have reported, there are typically a few times when people need to drive much farther.
正如特兰西克和同事们此前所报告的，现有较便宜的电动汽车所提供的续航里程就能满足人们绝大部分的日常驾驶需求，但通常总有那么几次，人们需要开得远得多。
Or, they may need to make more short trips than usual in a day, with little time to stop and recharge.
又或者，他们一天之内需要跑的短途可能比平时多，几乎没有时间停下来充电。
These “high-energy days,” as the researchers call them, when drivers are consuming more than the usual amount of energy for their transportation needs, may only happen a handful of times per year, but they can be the deciding factor in people’s decision making about whether to go electric.
研究人员所说的这些“高能耗日”，即驾驶者为满足出行需求而消耗的能源比平时多的日子，一年或许只有寥寥几次，但在人们决定是否改用电动汽车时，它们却可能成为决定性因素。
Even though battery technology is steadily improving and extending the maximum range of electric cars, that alone will not be enough to meet all drivers’ needs and achieve rapid emissions reductions.
尽管电池技术正在稳步改进，不断延长电动汽车的最大续航里程，但仅靠这一点并不足以满足所有驾驶者的需求、实现快速减排。
So, addressing the range issue through infrastructure is essential, Wei says.
魏伟说，因此，通过基础设施来解决续航问题至关重要。
The highest-capacity batteries tend to be the most expensive, and are not affordable to many, he points out, so getting infrastructure right is also important from an equity perspective.
他指出，容量最大的电池往往价格最高，许多人负担不起，因此，从公平的角度看，把基础设施做好也很重要。
“There are various ways to incentivize the expansion of such charging infrastructures,” he says.
他说：“以激励措施推动这类充电基础设施扩建的方式多种多样。”
“There’s a role for policymakers at the national level, for example, for incentives to encourage private sector competition in this space, and demonstration sites for testing out, through public-private partnerships, the rapid expansion of the charging infrastructure.”
“例如，国家层面的政策制定者就可以发挥作用：出台激励措施，鼓励私营部门在这一领域展开竞争，并设立示范点，通过公私合作来试验充电基础设施的快速扩建。”
Governments at different levels can also play an important part in driving innovation by businesses, he says, and a number of them have already signaled their support for vehicle electrification.
他说，各级政府也可以在推动企业创新方面发挥重要作用，而且已有一些政府表明了对车辆电气化的支持。
Providing easy access to alternative transportation for those high-energy days could also play a role, the study found.
研究发现，在那些“高能耗日”让人们能方便地使用替代交通工具，也可能发挥作用。
Vehicle companies may even find it advantageous to provide or partner with convenient rental services to help drive their electric car sales.
汽车公司甚至可能会发现，为帮助带动自家电动汽车的销售，自行提供便捷的租车服务或与此类租车服务商合作，是有利之举。
In their analysis of driving habits, for example, the team found that the impact of either adding highway fast-charging stations or increasing availability of supplementary long-range vehicles for up to four days a year meant that the number of homes that could meet their driving needs with a lower-cost electric vehicle increased from 10 percent to 40 percent.
例如，该团队在分析驾驶习惯时发现，无论是增设高速公路快速充电站，还是让人们每年最多有4天能更容易地用上长续航的补充车辆，其效果都是：靠一辆较便宜的电动汽车就能满足自身驾驶需求的家庭比例从10%升至40%。
This number rose to above 90 percent of households when fast-charging stations, workplace charging, overnight public charging, and up to 10 days of access to supplementary vehicles were all available.
在快速充电站、工作场所充电、夜间公共充电以及最多10天的补充车辆使用机会全都具备的情况下，这一数字升至家庭总数的90%以上。
Importantly, charging options at residential locations (on- or off-street) are key across all of these scenarios.
重要的是，在所有这些情景下，住处的充电选择（路内或路外）都是关键。
The study’s findings highlight the importance of making overnight charging capabilities available to more people.
这项研究的结果凸显了让更多人具备夜间充电条件的重要性。
While those who have their own garages or off-street parking can often already easily charge their cars at home, many people do not have that option and use public parking.
有自家车库或路外停车位的人往往已经可以在家轻松地给车充电，但许多人没有这种选择，用的是公共停车场。
“It’s really important to provide access—reliable, predictable access—to charging for people, wherever they park for longer periods of time near home, often overnight,” Trancik says.
特兰西克说：“真的很重要的一点是，无论人们在住处附近的什么地方较长时间停车（往往是过夜），都要为他们提供充电条件——可靠、可预期的充电条件。”
That includes locations such as hotels as well as residential neighborhoods, she says.
她说，这包括酒店之类的地方，也包括住宅区。
“I think it’s so critical to emphasize these high-impact approaches, such as figuring out ways to do that on public streets, rather than haphazardly putting a charger at the grocery store or at the mall or any other public location.”
“我认为，重视这些影响大的做法非常关键，比如想办法在公共街道上做到这一点，而不是随随便便地在杂货店、购物中心或其他任何公共场所装个充电桩。”
The study should help to provide some guidance to policymakers at all levels who are looking for ways to facilitate the reduction of greenhouse gas emissions, since the transportation sector accounts for about a third of those emissions overall.
这项研究应该有助于为正在想方设法推动温室气体减排的各级政策制定者提供一些指导，因为交通运输部门的排放约占温室气体排放总量的三分之一。
“If you have limited funds, which you typically always do, then it’s just really important to prioritize,” Trancik says, noting that this study could indicate the areas that could provide the greatest return for those investments.
特兰西克说：“如果资金有限——通常总是如此——那么排定优先次序就真的非常重要。”她还指出，这项研究或许能指明，把这些资金投向哪些领域能获得最大的回报。